

JunWei Song

Security Researcher

Contact

Taiwan

sungboss2004@gmail.com

https://github.com/krnick

in /krnick

<u>@JunWei_Song</u>

Education

National University of Kaohsiung, Master in Information Management, 2020

<u>Public</u> Speaking

Security Related:

- Black Hat Asia Arsenal 2021
- Oh My H@ck 2021
- DEFCON 28 Blue Team Village
- HITB Lockdown 002
- ROOTCON 2020
- Grayhat 2020

PyCon Related:

- Europython 2020
- PyCon India 2020
- PyCon Taiwan 2020/2019
- Pycon Korea 2019
- PyCon Malaysia 2019

Open Source:

• COSCUP 2021

Personal Profile

JunWei is a security researcher and open-source enthusiast from Taiwan. A paranoid Pythonista and CPython contributor who now focuses on Android reverse engineering and malware analysis. And as a member of the PyCon Taiwan Program Committee, previously presented at Black Hat, DEFCON, HITB, ROOTCON, GrayHat, PyCon Europe/TW/KR/MY/IN. He's the co-founder of Quark-Engine and the Quark package maintainer on Kali Linux, leading Quark to participate in the GSoC under the Honeynet Project since 2021.

Work Experience

Telecom Technology Center, Taiwan, Security Researcher

October 2018 - Now (Almost 3 years) - working during master's degree

Develop an Android malware scoring system from zero to one, as Lead Developer, in charge of Quark core function design, program development, program testing, documentation writing. Communicate and coordinate with team members, and cooperate through Gitflow. Also actively promote this project to train new members.

Using open source tools such as Jadx, radare2, ghidra and quark-engine (developed by me) to investigate whether there are potential malicious behaviors inside the Android applications.

Dowton Electronic Materials, Taiwan, Independent Contractor for network infrastructure

March 2017 - June 2017 (3 months) - working during college

Galaxy Software Services Corporation, Taiwan, Web Development Intern

July 2016 - August 2016 (2 months) - working during college

Vulnerability Research

<u>CVE-2019-9674</u>: zip bomb in Python zipfile module.

Technical Blog



<u>CPython-internals</u>

Analysis of CPython interpreter implementation principles and CPython source code analysis.

Books Reviewer



- 職業駭客的修練:機械碼與底層的把玩藝術
- 職業駭客的告白II部曲:
 Python和Ruby啟發式程式語
 言的秘密
- 職業駭客的告白III部曲:C語 言、組合語言與逆向工程的秘 密
- <u>駭客的修練:使用IDA Pro進</u> 行底層分析

PyCon TW Community



- PyCon Taiwan Program Committee since 2020
- PyCon Taiwan Review Board since 2020

Authored Open-Source Projects

Quark-Engine



An Obfuscation-Neglect Android Malware Scoring System.

sunzip

a Python package, providing secure unzip against zip bomb.

Open-Source Contributions

CPython



- 1. Find the Zip Bomb vulnerability and successfully apply for a CVE number in Python zipfile module.
- 2. Writing zipfile module decompression pitfalls in Python official documentation.

Androguard



Adding new feature, docs enhancement.

Rizin



Help refactor resource-allocating operations.